Minister
I don't know what you're talking about...
Is this information reliable?
Satellite information is reliable
The problem is that North Korea
How did you make it?
Without cooperation between China and Russia
It's impossible
Then they already
I mean, I condoned it.
North Korea has nuclear missiles
I will come to negotiations prepared to shoot.
They can shoot
President is coming
Please sit down
hello
thank you
- Be careful.
- Okay.
hello
This is the person I contacted
I had a dream
In my dream I
It was a woman
To the people of Korea
North Koreans are not just anyone
millions of our people
family and relatives
It's hundreds of kilometers away in North Korea.
we still have them
I feel like a brother
In the distant future we
When I look back on what I did today
just like us
Deserving of a human life
For the people of North Korea
I hope I can say I did the right thing
I sincerely hope
Even in the rain and wind
i wanted to run
Rep. Jang is the security guard.
Since when did you tell me to strengthen it?
- yes?
- It wasn't like this from the beginning, right?
He was obviously being careful about something.
Please tell me, Changhee.
About Rep. Jang
You know better than anyone else.
A month or two ago...
Suddenly, there are a lot of personal calls.
Attendees unknown
Security meetings have become more frequent
Senator, where are you...
The day before the ambassador's arrival
Especially when you're anxious
Double the number of security personnel.
Even a simple road suddenly tells me to turn around
Is it because of something?
May I ask you a question, Senator?
A squirrel is chasing me
Squirrel?
When Junsang was young
I got hit by a squirrel
You have a scar on your face
Who?
master?
So his nickname was Squirrel.
violent squirrel
It's exactly the same, right?
Uh, Mr. Midge.
Yongjun Kim's family
You told me to find out.
To see my father
I came to the front of the house
I guess you're going a long way
I have a lot of baggage
The whole family is in a big car.
With a slightly distraught face
There are people who help
Doesn't that seem like family?
Someone is stealing it
I have something to hide
I'll follow along.
No, because it can be dangerous.
It's me
Divorce lawyer from Tagari
Following is basic.
Tell me which direction, let's go together
until I go
Never get out of the car
last sunday
The Northern Catacombs
visit grandma
Rice and bread
A bundle containing a letter
I threw it in the yard
You look healthy, right?
The letter says you will be there the day after tomorrow
To China
I wrote that I would bring him out.
As a sign that the grandmother knew well,
He hung his white jeogori on the clothesline.
Go to China today
Today?
The situation is not serious
If you don't hurry
I can't go in
What's the situation, Father?
Michael Jang Jun-ik
There is a meaning left for me
What should I do with this?
You kept asking God
The cathedral will soon be noisy
What did Rep. Jang mean?
please let me know too
If he was killed for that
The bride will also be in danger.
That's
Between me, Michael, and the Lord
I made a promise
You go in faster than that
Come out with your grandmother.
Otherwise
I'll live the rest of my life in pain
I guess it has something to do with North Korea.
It's a statue of Saint Anthony
You've kept me safe so far
yes
Three adults, one child
There are a total of four people
One way ticket to Melbourne, Australia today
Is this correct?
yes, that's right
‘One way to Melbourne, Australia’?
Wait a minute
Excuse me
Let me ask you something.
I can't connect...
Master
Yeo Mi-ji, born in 1988
Where did you get such talent?
Very independent activist
Where are you?
I'm not doing the newspaper now.
I'm talking about talking
I made it clear
'Unconditionally
'It has nothing to do with the ambassador'
‘I will exercise my right to remain silent’
Oh, it hurts
Where are you?
Sister-in-law
Did you speak informally just now?
Even if you come here
can you do that
Let me take a look
Yes?
What are you doing now, sister-in-law?
I want to know why my husband died
The police should have told you
opposed to unification
He was killed by a crazy person.
Why did you follow Junik?
Did you really think I killed him?
Working in the dark
It's always like that
Even to my family
If you are treated like this...
Sister-in-law, I am for my brother.
what are you doing
You can't even imagine
Shall I tell you?
I am a former public security prosecutor in Korea.
The reason I followed my brother
My brother was a spy
No
without any evidence
Would you say something like this?
After catching the charges
Personally, I formed a separate team.
I'm trying to cover this up.
with all the evidence
all the circumstances
Why?
At any time, inter-Korean relations
In a place that can change suddenly
South Korean presidential candidate
If it turns out that you are a spy
What will society be like?
If the force that killed my brother
What if it's North Korea?
There could be war
If it turns out to be related to the US
There will be a big blow to the ROK-US alliance.
Junik's death
It has something to do with America?
We will meet again alive, right?
Uh, yeah
This wine is yours
Be sure to come back and drink it
Could you give this to me?
a dark road
I think I'll try relying on this.
My young friend, my son
You must be safe and safe again.
In the name of the Father, the Son and the Holy Spirit
Amen
An American named Baek San-ho
The Valkyrie Group
This is American mercenary company Ace.
You know?
Kill anyone who gives you money
Even people who are trash
people who protect
People like us
Because I figure it out first.
Who are people like us?
people without their own country
Why is that person
Were you at the scene of the incident?
Was it just a coincidence?
Do you understand now?
Why I Should Be President
our family, our country
And for world peace
I will cover everything.
Then think about it
my mom
Handsome, gentle and humorous
The world's smartest son
If you find out you're a spy
Wow, that's terrible.
Master was always jealous of his older brother.
I wanted you to fall over
I wanted to take that place
Have you got the opportunity of a lifetime?
yes
I can feel how excited you are.
By the way
I know my husband well.
Although it may be foolish and cowardly
I'm not a spy
You have proof?
But why did someone put so much effort into
Do you feel like you were prepared?
an innocent person
Evidence that makes you a spy
You guys are the experts.
who is a spy
What is evidence?
we decide
That's what keeps Korea going
It's the minimum act of governance.
An act of governing?
What are you guys?
The real reason Junik died
i find out
I don't know about world peace
I also have peace in my heart
Because I need to find it
I really love my sister-in-law
I wanted to treat you well
But I can't help it
I really hate it this way
Mr. Midge
This is my blood
How can you bite a sitting prosecutor?
Do you think you will be safe?
How dare you ask?
you guys
Organize everything within 24 hours
I'm going abroad
Yeo Mi-ji, I heard you were born late.
Otherwise, my old parents
A daughter who has no contact for a long time
You will be waiting
I want to talk to Miji.
What is power?
Doing something the other person doesn't want to do
It's the power that forces you to do it.
I really like power
Ambassador
I'm here, Mr. Midge.
very close
I'm fine, were you worried?
From now on, just think about one thing
Within 24 hours
Return safely to your parents
Ambassador, is it because of me?
These fucking bastards are making fucking demands.
You’re not listening, are you?
Don't worry about anything else
trust me
I'll solve it by morning
I believe it
Our Mr. Midge
If even a single hair gets hurt
I won't stay still
The promise is
Let's protect each other like a sword
Father, this is Seo Moon-ju.
Father?
Wait a minute
Stay still
passed away
I'll report it to the police
I have to go before then
But someone here
There's something I was trying to find
Why did you do that to the priest?
What are you looking for!
whale in the deep sea
Father
What's going on, are you inside?
rev!
Bring me the keys
Hey there
People out there will help you
Oh, I...
I really have to ask you something.
The kids' father is gone
I opened the tea room door for the first time.
Have you been here before?
Are you there?
I only heard the words
Old men who were worried about their country
I heard you meet here often.
As you know, in this room
You can say anything.
It is completely secure
To the Director’s prosperity
I paid a lot of attention
Why did you do that?
I'm the chairman
With the deceased minister
There was no special relationship
When I see my wife
I know what kind of person my husband is.
Having served as a generals' wives' club for over 40 years,
I have never met a person as good as your wife.
If such a woman is the man she has loved all her life
He must be a very respectable person, right?
I'm uncomfortable here today
I wasn't going to come out
My wife jumped up and down.
Chairman, if you turn away when times are difficult,
we are not people
And then
They don't tell me why...
Director
When was the most difficult time in your life?
When the little one is sick...
Please schedule the surgery then.
The person who even paid for it...
I told you not to tell me
So that my husband doesn't worry about me
Because it's our job
Okay then, Director.
Even after the death of our eldest child, Junik
Is America involved?
I don't know
But recently
Anderson Miller
U.S. Assistant Secretary of State
leak of national secrets
on charges of violating the Espionage Act
Being chased by the FBI
There was intelligence
That person
The person to whom the letter was sent is
My name is Rep. Jang Jun-ik.
I guess there was some kind of misunderstanding...
Actually we
Even before my son died
I was watching closely
Why?
There were suspicions of espionage.
It was said that there was secret communication with North Korea.
right here at home
This doesn't make sense.
Chairman
This house is being monitored
Are you the president?
my son
Someone trying to make you a spy?
beware of this man
interest belongs to
The group called Valkyrie itself
Anything as long as you give me money
These are people who do it all
Who did you get the money from?
For what purpose did you approach it?
I don't know
What is this?
It has been around since the Japanese colonial period.
It's an underground passage.
Connected to both North and South Korea
This underground church
It was called the catacombs.
including the priest and me
Only a few people know
Affiliated with the private military company Valkyrie
I heard you were a mercenary.
In Valkyrie
The contract is renewed every 1 or 2 years.
My contract ended a year ago
did not renew the contract
The scene of the death of my husband and priest
It was the closest one
Is it a coincidence?
here
It’s a tunnel 12 meters underground.
If you thought I was in danger
Mr. Seo Moon-ju
You shouldn't have followed me in here.
This was in the priest's Bible.
Puncture marks on the back of the priest's hand
He was killed by poison.
The general public will never
This method cannot be used.
That person, in the priest's room
You were looking for something.
The priest will attend mass tomorrow
Rep. Jang Jun-ik’s message
He said he would tell it.
Rep. Jang said after mass that day,
I was planning to announce something.
This is Mayangdo Island
Near Yeongpo Shipyard
‘Dear Junik’
'This was two weeks ago by the Defense Intelligence Agency.
'This is a satellite photo I obtained.'
A 10,000-ton nuclear submarine
This object is believed to be...
It has a total length of 140 meters
It is estimated to be a 10,000-ton nuclear submarine.
16 state-of-the-art SLBMs
A vertical launch tube is installed
Up to 128 nuclear warheads
It can be mounted
If this prediction turns out to be true
North Korea's nuclear threat
It can be seen that it has become a reality
Damn it
That's right
you obviously
Submarines made by North Korea
It's a 3,000-ton rattle.
Didn't you?
One day that disgusting guy
What if you wanted to drop a nuclear bomb on this land?
What are you going to do then?
-Why do you do things like this?
- Minister, I don't know what you're talking about...
- I...
- Shut up, I don't need an answer.
This is
It was a huge shock
two months from now
North Korean National Defense Chairman
On Kim Han-sang’s birthday
A submarine launching ceremony will be held.
Mr. President
We use low-yield nuclear bombs
Yeongpo Shipyard, Nuclear Bomb Storage
nuclear submarine base, etc.
A total of 40 locations
We plan to strike with precision.
Our military authorities
With simultaneous precision strikes
North Korea's related military facilities
completely annihilate
I'm planning a special operation
Our missile guidance system is
With 98 percent accuracy
I am confident that we will destroy our target.
I have a question
What is the possibility of the war expanding to the entire Korean Peninsula?
Herman Institute's
According to the report
A preemptive strike against North Korea turns into an all-out war.
32 percent chance of expansion
There is a possibility that it will end in a local war
It is predicted to be 41 percent
But if it escalates into an all-out war,
All of East Asia
Likely to become a battlefield
I think it's very high
something is wrong
North Korea will build such a submarine
I have no capital or technology.
the existence of submarines
I'll check again
If the outbreak spreads, millions
You can be sacrificed
no, you don't need to
This operation will be over in 5 minutes
This is the war of the future
Future weapons, future strategies
The history of future warfare
It will be used from here
And you know what?
From the beginning, you pretended to be American.
I didn't like it
From today onwards you cannot come in here.
It's a presidential order.
I have a Korean face
Always in Korea
Supported the most hostile policies
Because it works well in Washington
But this plan
It has to be reconsidered
Help me, Junik
my cell phone and laptop
all electronic devices
Because you can be monitored
When replying, please send it by secure email.
Using the enclosed encryption key
As soon as I read this letter
I hope you give me a ride
'Anderson Miller'
U.S. Assistant Secretary of State
in Georgetown
I did a doctoral course together with my husband.
Representative Jang Jun-ik
About this letter that day
I guess they were trying to make an announcement.
To prevent war
The priest also suddenly today
He urged me to go to North Korea.
Because there could be war
Do you have family in North Korea?
Then you should hurry up and go.
I will take charge of this letter.
Because of this
You could be in danger
Does it still matter?
yes
This is the only way
My husband was also alive
I was going to do that
Are you trustworthy?
The strongest in Korea
He is a trustworthy person.
Baek San-ho, you can go your way now.
I'll do it from here on out
going to war
He is the patron saint of warriors.
The priest gave it to me
I think I'll get in trouble on the long road
Yes, manager.
I know what you mean.
I suddenly
I feel like I'm someone I can't meet
Of course I know it well
It doesn’t have to be right away.
Maybe within today
If I could see you even for a moment
I'll wait here
no
I don't mean to burden you
I have some really urgent business...
Why like this
Did you bother our manager?
Sorry, Mr. President.
There was a situation
Even though I know it's an unreasonable request
I'm so urgent...
Our military authorities
With simultaneous precision strikes
North Korea's related military facilities
completely annihilate
I'm planning a special operation
But this plan
It has to be reconsidered
Help me, Junik
Rep. Jang said to the President:
I think I was trying to discuss it.
Let's work together to solve the problem
Why did Rep. Jang
Couldn't he have burned the letter?
Then Father Yang Inbo also
He probably didn't die.
In a difficult situation
I wouldn't have been punished
A few days after Rep. Jang's death
Our intelligence agents and the American kids
I was moving dizzy
After understanding the situation to some extent,
I and Rep. Jang
reached the same conclusion
‘War must be prevented no matter what’
To do that, first get out of your own way.
Yes?
This is not diplomacy, this is war
crazy guy game
Two crazy guys running at full speed
Driving towards each other
I won't stop so you should avoid me
we stand in the middle
‘Guys, don’t fight.
'Let's resolve it peacefully'
No matter how much I wave the flag and shout
Can you hear me?
So what are you going to do?
Hop into that crazy guy's car
I need to change the direction I run
Preface
Do you know what your problem is?
Being truthful as a diplomat is grounds for disqualification.
In a weak country
Someone needs to take care of our situation
Something falls
When doing diplomacy
That kind of charm
It was useful sometimes, but
Like the Hauser regime
against a hostile opponent
When engaging in unfriendly multilateral diplomacy
you were useless
the spot
Do you think you quit on your own?
It was cut off
Lying and using shallow tricks
Fraud, trickery, betrayal
Even if it's like that
Because I can't bring the results
I was pushed out
Look
Because even now, I’m being stabbed in the back.
You're surprised
Listen carefully
Death in war is not murder
Her husband's death
politically
It has to be handled diplomatically.
i will do that
Knowing who killed it
Does that mean you're just going to cover it up?
Jang Jun-ik, squeezing through the gap created by death
I'm going to hop in an American car
So you're out
Are you interested in NGOs?
It suits you perfectly
anywhere
Go to the fastest place you can go
It's not advice, it's not a request
It's an order
What if you don't do that?
To me
We must prevent war on the Korean Peninsula.
I have a responsibility, this
more than you think
It's a much bigger board
“Ethan”
From money
Let's go
I decided where to go
I'll get out of the room as quickly as possible.
one thing
Let me ask you a question, mother.
Junik and I get married
Why were you so opposed to it?
Cut everything off
You said you'd never see me again
I told my son
happy and warm woman
I wanted to pair you up.
You're a dark and cold child
I felt like I was going to be unhappy
In the end it happened like that
He later gave permission.
So
I know you could have gotten married.
On the outside, this family
It seems like my father is moving
What decides everything
It was actually my mother.
before marriage
I found out more about you
Mother alone in America
You raised a daughter.
Did you have a hard time?
Nail shop, hospital cleaning, supermarket cashier
There's nothing I haven't done
By the time you go back
Junik is at your house
I even did nursing.
I gave a mock United Nations speech in college.
After becoming famous
I saw your interview by chance
Put the Taegeukgi in the room
young man studying
There are patriotic young people in South Korea.
It's very rare
I'm always in my country
I wanted to be accepted
Being Korean
It's been my wish for a long time
That's it
We are Junik
I wanted to do politics
Is this a long-term investment spanning three generations?
But Junik lacked something.
What I can never fill
Ah
That's patriotism
So I recognized you
to become president
The partner I need most is you
Let me ask you one more question.
Do you still think that way?
In the presidential election, you are not a brat.
I have to go out
Junsang has been hateful since he was young.
Junik was very popular.
and you
There's something special about it
What should I say?
people bet on you
not to win
If I'm with you
With the feeling that it doesn't matter if I fail
If I were an election planner
I will choose you
Some characteristics can be honed, but
Because some characteristics are unique
When Junik was young,
He was able to become a strong presidential candidate
It's my mother's plan.
I know it well
Political parties, media, companies, regions
You prepared all of this.
over several decades
Why are you telling me this?
I thought you were in pain.
Those countless stairs
I cleaned everything one by one.
Just a few steps left
I fell
So when I hold out my hand
I thought you could catch it.
Even though you hate me
You can start again from that spot
It's your only chance
If Junik
property issues
If you hadn't handled it that way
I would have pitied you
Losing a husband, losing a child
All women are different
Sometimes everything is the same
the stairs I left behind
I want to go up, mother.
Today too
I think it was wrong to go in.
My today is
You must cross
My family is waiting for me
Don't you know
When I die, what about my family?
It's all over!
I can't get over it, the riverside is blocked.
It's been a few days
The storm army has been completely crushed.
What are you talking about suddenly?
Just cross, that's how they all go
Run! Run!
Get in the water!
So let's talk business.
What do you want from me?
What are you going to do for me?
Junik played
Right on the spot
please let me run
If I get elected
Everything Junik gave me
I'll give it to my mother
This house will also be in my mother’s name.
If you are elected as a presidential candidate
Where to go to overseas property
Are you going to scrape it all off?
If this were a scene from a novel
I think the author will write it like this
'She's been waiting a long time'
‘My husband died’
'Your lost dream
The day I can get it back'
What does it say there?
That was your dream
Tell me, where should we start?
What do you want me to do for you?
Please call the master.
My aide Yeo Mi-ji
Please send me home right away
And within 24 hours
Withdraw your candidacy
Master, you need to go abroad.
Father!
Father, wake up!
You are the Lord
I know you don't believe it
You say a prayer with your mouth
The soul does not seek God
Only with your strength
Trying to do it all
But honey
Because you don't know God
We must not be ignorant of human love.
Why do I love humans
Do you think you don't know?
Humans want to find love
It's about leaving your hometown and wandering the world.
for you to return to your hometown
Didn't you risk everything?
To prevent war
Because of this
You could be in danger
Does it still matter?
yes
Tell it to the client
I will take care of that woman